farebuzz.com 2007-08-28

# Fare Buzz - Privacy Policy

**

Fare Buzz is Strongly Sommitted to Protecting Your Privacy

** ****We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.  We keep your personal information private and secure.  When you become a member of our program, you provide your name, email address and other information. We use this information to answer your questions and process your requests.

This web site uses cookies to personalize your experience at this site, and optionally to speed up the member sign in process.  Cookies are information stored on your computer.  Cookies are not used to track your movement or perform any function other than to enhance your use of this site.  If your browser does not support cookies, or you have not enabled cookies on your browser, many of these time-saving features will not work properly.  Also, you need to have cookies enabled in your browser if you want to enter the member's area. 

To keep you informed about our latest services, we may notify you via email newsletter of any changes or new additions to our site.  You may unsubscribe from our email newsletter by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email you receive from us. 

Other sites accessible through our web site have their own privacy policies and data collection practices.  Please consult each site's privacy policy. **  Fare Buzz** is not responsible for the actions of third parties.

****  
Customer Information Security****

  1. Personally Identifiable Information is collected when: 

a. The online customer submits traveler information at the time of booking a reservation.

b. The customer registers on the site and becomes a member.

c. The customer registered in 1b adds profile of other customers.

d. Travel arrangers register on the site to book travel for their clients.

e. Customers sign up for special promotions and sweepstakes.

f. Contact customer service through online customer care center. 
  2. Security of Information:

a. The credit card information is collected on a Secured Socket Layer (128 bit SSL) secured page and is directly sent to the online processor for verification.

b. We do not store credit card information in our system. The credit card information is stored at the facilities of our online transaction processing company.

c. We store the personally identifiable information within secured DMZ environment which is housed inside robust firewalls.

  3. Use of information:

a. We do not sell any personally identifiable information to our business partners, affiliates and third party companies.

b. We use the customer information to send them travel deals and promotions, booking related confirmation emails and newsletter.
